<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Congregation Beth Shalom - Dover Synagogue]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Congregation Beth Shalom - Dover Synagogue]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/congregation-beth-shalom-dover-synagogue/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 16:06:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/congregation-beth-shalom-dover-synagogue/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Word From Our President]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Congregation Beth Sholom is committed to providing a Jewish organization in Central Delaware. We have been in existence since incorporating in 1946. Our building was dedicated in 1963 and has been continually updated and modernized to keep pace with energy efficiency, handicapped accessibility, and maintains comfortable surroundings. Although we are a small congregation, our philosophy is to maintain an egalitarian setting with strong rabbinical support and opportunities for educational and spiritual growth. We practice traditional prayer services on Friday nights and Saturday mornings. Saturday services are suspended during the summer months of July and August. Our Rabbi conducts the High Holiday services and Shabbat services on a monthly basis. While our lay leaders provide alternate leadership in the interim, our choir and young post bar/bat mitzvah teens supplement other Shabbat services. We offer Jewish history and religious classes for all ages. There are plenty of opportunities for newcomers to meet our warm and friendly congregants. And we welcome you to participate in living Jewishly --- Caroline Schwartz, President </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/congregation-beth-shalom-dover-synagogue/a-word-from-our-president/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8384fdaa-fe68-4d7e-8540-dafe5c4313a1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 16:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>